<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<feed>
	<!-- resultLength indicates the total number of results for this feed -->
	<resultLength>4</resultLength>
	<!-- endIndix  indicates the number of results for this *paged* section of the feed -->
	<endIndex>4</endIndex>
	<item sdImg="http://s3.amazonaws.com/roku-creation-channel/CreationTruthFoundation/Images/DrSharp/The_Truth_About_Dinosaurs.jpg" hdImg="http://s3.amazonaws.com/roku-creation-channel/CreationTruthFoundation/Images/DrSharp/The_Truth_About_Dinosaurs.jpg">
		<title>The Truth About Dinosaurs</title>
		<contentId>12001</contentId>
		<contentType></contentType>
		<contentQuality>HD</contentQuality>
		<media>
			<streamFormat>mp4</streamFormat>
			<streamQuality>HD</streamQuality>
			<streamBitrate>0</streamBitrate>
			<streamUrl><![CDATA[http://s3.amazonaws.com/roku-creation-channel/MuseumOfEarthHistory/Videos/The_Beauty_of_Pollination.mp4]]></streamUrl>
		</media>
		<synopsis>Discover the Biblical reality about dinosaurs! In this stunning program, watch science and the Bible unite as you learn the amazing truth about these creatures. Using more than 28 museum-quality dinosaur fossils and specimens, Dr. Sharp will explain the Biblical view of dinosaurs’ origins and disappearance as he walks you through the five most frequently asked questions about dinosaurs: Did dinosaurs really exist? If so, when did they exist? Where are they now? Why are dinosaurs not in the Bible? Were dinosaurs on Noah’s Ark? Dr. Sharp will also reveal their fascinating history and the role they play in your worldview. Come learn the Truth About Dinosaurs.</synopsis>
		<genres>Presentation</genres>
		<runtime>3278</runtime>
		<date>02/22/2012</date>
	</item>	
	<item sdImg="http://s3.amazonaws.com/roku-creation-channel/CreationTruthFoundation/Images/DrSharp/A_Thousand_Years_In_A_Day.jpg" hdImg="http://s3.amazonaws.com/roku-creation-channel/CreationTruthFoundation/Images/DrSharp/A_Thousand_Years_In_A_Day.jpg">
		<title>A Thousand Years in a Day</title>
		<contentId>12002</contentId>
		<contentType></contentType>
		<contentQuality>HD</contentQuality>
		<media>
			<streamFormat>mp4</streamFormat>
			<streamQuality>HD</streamQuality>
			<streamBitrate>0</streamBitrate>
			<streamUrl><![CDATA[http://s3.amazonaws.com/roku-creation-channel/MuseumOfEarthHistory/Videos/The_Beauty_of_Pollination.mp4]]></streamUrl>
		</media>
		<synopsis>The Mt. St. Helens Catastrophe By Dr. G. Thomas Sharp Did you know that God can and has used natural processes in a supernatural way to impact the surface of the earth with thousands of years of change in only ONE day? What do you suppose happened when “all of the fountains of the great deep opened” at the beginning of the Flood of Noah? When you look at the canyons, mountains, rock layers and fossils of the earth, how do you explain them? The Bible has sound, reasonable explanations for these marvelous observations. Did you know that in 1980 an eleven-year process was begun at Mt. St. Helens that epitomized on a small scale the action and results of the Great Genesis Flood…that it was proven that God could take a catastrophe and do the geological work of thousands, even millions, of years in ONE day? In this program, G. Dr. Sharp will be your guide through the seconds, minutes and days the eye-opening action of catastrophic earth slides, tidal-like waves, mud flows and other residual effects of the history-making Mt. St. Helens Catastrophe. You will see, with your own eyes, the ability of catastrophic action do the work of thousands of years…IN JUST ONE DAY!</synopsis>
		<genres>Presentation</genres>
		<runtime>2952</runtime>
		<date>12/19/2011</date>
	</item>	
	<item sdImg="http://s3.amazonaws.com/roku-creation-channel/CreationTruthFoundation/Images/DrSharp/Design_The_Evolutionary_Nightmare.jpg" hdImg="http://s3.amazonaws.com/roku-creation-channel/CreationTruthFoundation/Images/DrSharp/Design_The_Evolutionary_Nightmare.jpg">
		<title>Design: The Evolutionary Nightmare</title>
		<contentId>12003</contentId>
		<contentType></contentType>
		<contentQuality>HD</contentQuality>
		<media>
			<streamFormat>mp4</streamFormat>
			<streamQuality>HD</streamQuality>
			<streamBitrate>0</streamBitrate>
			<streamUrl><![CDATA[http://s3.amazonaws.com/roku-creation-channel/MuseumOfEarthHistory/Videos/The_Beauty_of_Pollination.mp4]]></streamUrl>
		</media>
		<synopsis>The earth—tilted at the perfect degree to maintain the right conditions for life on this planet. The sun—located at the perfect distance from the earth to provide light and heat without destroying vital life elements. Living organisms—working inexplicably together to sustain life. There is only one thing that can explain these wonders: Intelligent Design. This design can be seen everywhere, from the location of stars and galaxies to the most intricate details of nature. In this program, Dr. Sharp will guide you through our amazing universe, pointing out the handprints of God that surround us. Hear the mathematical probabilities for these features happening by chance, and witness the flawless design of the omnipotent Creator.
</synopsis>
		<genres>Presentation</genres>
		<runtime>2495</runtime>
		<date>01/30/2012</date>
	</item>	
	<item sdImg="http://s3.amazonaws.com/roku-creation-channel/CreationTruthFoundation/Images/DrSharp/Americas_Christian_Heritage.jpg" hdImg="http://s3.amazonaws.com/roku-creation-channel/CreationTruthFoundation/Images/DrSharp/Americas_Christian_Heritage.jpg">
		<title>America's Christian Heritage</title>
		<contentId>12004</contentId>
		<contentType></contentType>
		<contentQuality>HD</contentQuality>
		<media>
			<streamFormat>mp4</streamFormat>
			<streamQuality>HD</streamQuality>
			<streamBitrate>0</streamBitrate>
			<streamUrl><![CDATA[http://s3.amazonaws.com/roku-creation-channel/MuseumOfEarthHistory/Videos/The_Beauty_of_Pollination.mp4]]></streamUrl>
		</media>
		<synopsis>What's a thinking Christian to do ... about today's "Oppositions of science, falsely so called" (1Tim 6:20)? Christians should always stick to the word, as their source of ultimate authority for questions about the origins or anything else. Still, many are swayed by the authoritative-sounding preaching of today's evo-evangelists .. and so compromise on the word of God, thinking they can make peace between these two warring ideas. What shape has this compromise effort taken? In every case, it becomes an "adding things to the word" situation. In many cases, it is a "taking away" from the word. In all cases, it requires a disregard for the divine revelation of God's truth to us. Such compromises require outright intellectual and spiritual dishonesties, uncharateristic of a true follower of Christ and His word. This DVD takes a critical look at several of the most popular honest errors of emphasis all the way through to the downright dishonest errors of blasphemy. You should be aware of these "oppositions of science falsely so called" which are being taught in many areas of the church today.</synopsis>
		<genres>Presentation</genres>
		<runtime>1954</runtime>
		<date>01/05/2012</date>
	</item>	
	<item sdImg="http://s3.amazonaws.com/roku-creation-channel/CreationTruthFoundation/Images/DrSharp/Evolutionism.jpg" hdImg="http://s3.amazonaws.com/roku-creation-channel/CreationTruthFoundation/Images/DrSharp/Evolutionism.jpg">
		<title>Evolutionism: The Greatest Deception of All Time</title>
		<contentId>12005</contentId>
		<contentType></contentType>
		<contentQuality>HD</contentQuality>
		<media>
			<streamFormat>mp4</streamFormat>
			<streamQuality>HD</streamQuality>
			<streamBitrate>0</streamBitrate>
			<streamUrl><![CDATA[http://s3.amazonaws.com/roku-creation-channel/MuseumOfEarthHistory/Videos/The_Beauty_of_Pollination.mp4]]></streamUrl>
		</media>
		<synopsis>Evolution has played one of the largest theological roles in history, affecting countless people and shifting the worldviews of entire civilizations. But where did this theory come from? What is its true history and foundational beliefs? Find out in this unprecedented program as Dr. Sharp guides you through the history, theories, and fallacies of evolution. Hear the remarkable words of the scientists themselves and explore the truth behind the movement. Discover the greatest deception of all.</synopsis>
		<genres>Presentation</genres>
		<runtime>2895</runtime>
		<date>02/22/2012</date>
	</item>	
	<item sdImg="http://s3.amazonaws.com/roku-creation-channel/CreationTruthFoundation/Images/DrSharp/The_Paganization_Of_America.jpg" hdImg="http://s3.amazonaws.com/roku-creation-channel/CreationTruthFoundation/Images/DrSharp/The_Paganization_Of_America.jpg">
		<title>The Paganization of America</title>
		<contentId>12006</contentId>
		<contentType></contentType>
		<contentQuality>HD</contentQuality>
		<media>
			<streamFormat>mp4</streamFormat>
			<streamQuality>HD</streamQuality>
			<streamBitrate>0</streamBitrate>
			<streamUrl><![CDATA[http://s3.amazonaws.com/roku-creation-channel/MuseumOfEarthHistory/Videos/The_Beauty_of_Pollination.mp4]]></streamUrl>
		</media>
		<synopsis>Why did America loose her Judeo/Christian worldview? Why are Christian families in America losing 70-80 percent of their children to a secular mind-set by the time they turn fifteen? Why did the U.S. Supreme Court rule in 1962-63 that prayer and Bible reading were unconstitutional for American school children? What significant leaven has crept into the fabric of America’s social conscience that permits a million and a half abortions each year since 1973? Did you know that Noah Webster, America’s Schoolmaster, said during our founding era, “…that the man who weakens or destroys the divine authority of the Bible may be accessory to all public disorders that society is doomed to suffer.” Has there been such a man? In this eye-opening program, G. Dr. Sharp will historically answer all of the above questions, as well as show you how America can reclaim Her former estate. This will be one of the most disturbing and beneficial presentations you will ever see.</synopsis>
		<genres>Presentation</genres>
		<runtime>1776</runtime>
		<date>02/20/2012</date>
	</item>	
	<item sdImg="http://s3.amazonaws.com/roku-creation-channel/CreationTruthFoundation/Images/DrSharp/Raising_Godly_Children.jpg" hdImg="http://s3.amazonaws.com/roku-creation-channel/CreationTruthFoundation/Images/DrSharp/Raising_Godly_Children.jpg">
		<title>Raising Godly Children</title>
		<contentId>12007</contentId>
		<contentType></contentType>
		<contentQuality>HD</contentQuality>
		<media>
			<streamFormat>mp4</streamFormat>
			<streamQuality>HD</streamQuality>
			<streamBitrate>0</streamBitrate>
			<streamUrl><![CDATA[http://s3.amazonaws.com/roku-creation-channel/MuseumOfEarthHistory/Videos/The_Beauty_of_Pollination.mp4]]></streamUrl>
		</media>
		<synopsis>In a world where we are bombarded with post-Christian ideals, the most difficult task parents face is raising godly children. This task is becoming exponentially harder in today’s culture; America has rejected its Christian foundation and become a predominately pagan society. Christian parents find themselves in the grip of this powerful dilemma. They want to raise their sons and daughters to be righteous, but the world bombards them with pagan principles. However, there is hope: God has a specific plan for your family—a kingdom vision established in his Word for you. In this much needed presentation, G. Dr. Sharp shows the demand, design and destiny for raising godly children, even in a pagan culture, and walks you through the steps that will lead you to God’s purpose for your family.</synopsis>
		<genres>Presentation</genres>
		<runtime>3181</runtime>
		<date>01/26/2012</date>
	</item>	

</feed>
